

#### CONTACT



Odolanow, Poland +48 729 233 897



fenix4088@gmail.com



# SOCIAL









#### **ABOUT**

Front-end developer with experience in creating SPA using React, Redux, TS, HTML, CSS. Determined to become a Full stack developer. Spend my free time improving competence in English and Polish, and expanding my professional horizons.

Self-motivated, hard-working, responsible and competent.

# **PROFESSIONAL SKILLS**

- React + Redux
- JavaScript/TypeScript
- HTML & CSS
- CSS pre-processors (SCSS)
- RestAPI, Axios, redux-thunk, reduxsaga
- Unit-test, Storybook, TDD, Postman
- Bootstrap, MaterialUI, Ant Design
- GIT, npm/yarn packages
- Photoshop, Figma, Avocode

# **LANGUAGES**

- Russian, Ukrainian (native);
- English Uper-intermediate
- Polish Uper-intermediate

# **PLIASOV YEHOR**

# FRONT-FND DEVELOPER

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Freelance | Nov 2020 - present

- React developer using React(Redux), redux-thunk, axios, formik
- Creating functional components with Hooks, using TypeScript
- Covering applications with tests
- Bugs fixing, creating forms and components libraries.

#### CARGO OPERATOR, LOGISTICIAN ASSISTANT

Awra group, Poland | Nov 2016 - Dec 2020

- Responsible for the storage of goods
- Working with clients, keeping stock records

# **TECHNICAL SUPERVISOR OF WELDING OPERATIONS AND SERVICES**

Technical college, Ukraine | Apr 2014 - Nov 2016

- Technical training of students
- Organization of professional excursions
- · Consulting graduates on employment

#### **EDUCATION**

# SPECIALIST IN WELDING TECHNOLOGIES AND EQUIPMENT

Engineering and Technology Faculty
Zaporizhzhia Technical University | 2013 - 2014

# **BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN WELDING TECHNOLOGIES AND EQUIPMENT**

Engineering and Technology Faculty Zaporizhzhia Technical University | 2009 - 2013

# TRAINING

#### **REACT DEVELOPER**

IT-Incubator | 2020

React, Redux, TypeScript, TDD, Storybook, Unit tests, creating SPA

# FRONT-END DEVELOPER

JavaScript.info | Aug 2020 - Nov 2020

JavaScript(OOP), working with DOM, Unit tests, creating classes components

# FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Webcademy | Apr 2020 - July 2020

JavaScript, working with DOM, Unit tests, Webpack

# FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Webcademy | March 2020 - May2020

 ${\sf HTML, CSS, SCSS/LESS, RWD/AWD, Pixel perfect, Bootstrap, JQuery}$